Imagine the cognitive dissonance that you have to exercise to really actually believe.
You know, when they let, I think the real number is 15, 16 million people into our country,
when they do that, we got a lot of work to do.
They're poisoning the blood of our country.
That's what they've done.
They poison mental institutions and prisons all over the world,
not just in South America, not just the three or four countries that we think about,
but all over the world, they're coming into our country from Africa, from Asia, all over the world.
They're pouring into our country.
Nobody's even looking at them.
They just come in.
I guess we call in season and poison now.
That's what it seems like.
You know what?
Can we just leave these people to their blandness, to their mediocrity?
It's just wild to me that knowing all the obstacles that have been put in the way,
and they know, even though they like the front, they don't,
that they still want to act like they are the supreme beings.
When we consistently surpass, we consistently innovate,
we consistently show up and show out.
Doesn't that tell you something?
That with all your privilege, you still just neck and neck?
That's why they be trying to put the foot on our necks.
Because they're like, if I could just know, you can't.
You can't, because that mindset has bred a certain DNA type
that likes to just keep people oppressed.
And then the rest of us, we have a certain DNA type that just won't quit.
I wish there was somewhere else for us to go.
Child.
To leave these fools to themselves.
They either shoot each other, rob each other,
or they'd end up eating each other.
It'd be Lord of the Plies up in this bitch.
To leave these fools, we'll be right back.